prince1 = [
  {"question":"正中央","Answer":"zhèng zhōngyāng"},
  {"question":"雕像","Answer":"diāoxiàng"},
  {"question":"渾身","Answer":"húnshēn"},
  {"question":"鑲滿","Answer":"xiāngmǎn"},
  {"question":"薄薄","Answer":"bóbó"},
  {"question":"藍寶石","Answer":"lánbǎoshí"},
  {"question":"劍柄","Answer":"jiàn bǐng"},
  {"question":"嵌著","Answer":"qiànzhe"},
  {"question":"座","Answer":"zuò"},
  {"question":"讚歎","Answer":"zàn tàn"},
  {"question":"教堂","Answer":"jiàotáng"},
  {"question":"互相追逐","Answer":"hùxiāng zhuīzhú"},
  {"question":"簇擁","Answer":"cùyōng"},
  {"question":"哇","Answer":"wā"},
  {"question":"城市","Answer":"chéngshì"},
  {"question":"往","Answer":"wǎng"},
  {"question":"南方","Answer":"nánfāng"},
  {"question":"埃及","Answer":"āijí"},
  {"question":"蘆葦","Answer":"lúwěi"},
  {"question":"柔軟","Answer":"róuruǎn"},
  {"question":"纖細","Answer":"xiānxì"},
  {"question":"振翅","Answer":"zhènchì"},
  {"question":"湊近","Answer":"còujìn"},
  {"question":"靦腆","Answer":"miǎntiǎn"},
  {"question":"欣喜若狂","Answer":"xīnxǐruòkuáng"},
  {"question":"繞著","Answer":"ràozhe"},
  {"question":"嬉戲","Answer":"xīxì"},
  {"question":"秋涼","Answer":"qiūliáng"},
  {"question":"一陣","Answer":"yīzhèn"},
  {"question":"孤寂感","Answer":"gūjì gǎn"},
  {"question":"襲上心頭","Answer":"xíshàng xīntóu"},
  {"question":"飛抵","Answer":"fēidǐ"},
  {"question":"站立","Answer":"zhànlì"},
  {"question":"圓柱","Answer":"yuánzhù"},
  {"question":"蜷縮","Answer":"quánsuō"},
  {"question":"臥室","Answer":"wòshì"},
  {"question":"閉上眼之際","Answer":"bìshang yǎnzhījì"},
  {"question":"顆","Answer":"kē"},
  {"question":"斗","Answer":"dǒu"},
  {"question":"燕子","Answer":"yànzi"},
  {"question":"張望","Answer":"zhāngwàng"},
  {"question":"毫無異狀","Answer":"háowúyì zhuàng"},
  {"question":"甚至","Answer":"shènzhì"},
  {"question":"清澈","Answer":"qīngchè"},
  {"question":"閃爍","Answer":"shǎnshuò"},
  {"question":"再度","Answer":"zàidù"},
  {"question":"緊接","Answer":"jǐnjiē"},
  {"question":"安穩","Answer":"ānwěn"},
  {"question":"翅膀","Answer":"chìbǎng"},
  {"question":"皺着","Answer":"zhòu zhe"}
]